Guide to the Russell and Sigurd Varian Papers
Stanford University Libraries.
- Photographs, 1869-1959; Series 10; 1.25 Linear feet
  - Sigurd-photographs of airplane, negatives (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Sigurd's house in Mexico (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Photograph of letter, Hansen to Russell Varian (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of letters, Stanford to John Easton (first proposal for Klystron development) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Agnes Varian, album, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Jack Varian (Sigurd and Jack; Christmas), 1959; 1968 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Varian Associates, Klystron (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Uncle Bill Varian, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Castle Rock, circa 1962 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Dorothy Varian, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Dorothy Varian, book signing at Varian Associates, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous family photographs (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Figures (glass slides) (Box 5)
- Dictaphone Recordings, Series 11
  - Audograph recordings (Box 1)
  - Recording machine (Box 2)
- Oversize Material & Objects, Series 12
  - Glasses; Russell's slide rule (Box 1)
  - "The Klystron Boys": Russell and Sigurd Varian by Roxanne Nilan (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Photographs; awards; Saturday Evening Post with typescript The story behind the 'Klystron Boys' article by Dorothy Varian pasted on cover. (Box 2, Folder 2)